Niagara-Orleans Labor Council Records 5419
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Niagara-Orleans Labor Council Records
1956-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Niagara-Orleans Labor Council
5419
4.33 cubic feet
4.3 linear ft.
Records (documents), minutes (administrative records), correspondence.
Minutes and correspondence from the Niagara-Orleans Labor Council
3338514
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Labor unions -- New York (State); Labor unions -- Political activity; Niagara-Orleans Labor Council
3338514
- Minutes, correspondence, and roll call books, 1956-1969 (Box 1)
  - Record Book - Attendance, 1957-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound Volume. January 16, 1957-April 16, 1969
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1969 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Minutes and correspondence, 1970-January 1973 (Box 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Niagara County American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Council - Labor Day Picnic, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Niagara County American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations Council - Labor Day Picnic (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1972 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1972 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1972 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1972 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1972 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Minutes and correspondence, February 1973-1975; Committee on Political Education, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1975 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Minutes and correspondence, 1976-February 1977 (Box 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Minutes and Correspondence, March 1977-February 1979 (Box 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Not endorsed, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - September 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Minutes and Correspondence, March 1979-August 1979; Miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - November 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - December 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - January 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - February 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - March 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - April 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - May 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - June 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - July 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - August 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Political Education - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Niagara County Legislators, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Councilmen and women - correspondence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Town Justices and City Court, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Candidates who lost or were not endorsed, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Supervisors, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Requests for Endorsement - Mayoral Candidates, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Towns and Orleans, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Mailing List, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    January 4, 1977; January 1978
  - 14(b), 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    1964-1966 and undated
  - Pamphlets, 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    1957-1959, 1971, 1973
  - Jesse Helms (Box 6, Folder 22)
    No date
  - Elections - Credentials and Tally Sheets, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - By-Laws (Box 6, Folder 24)